We will begin this exercise with a 3 -2 -1 method.
Find a comfortable position.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath and while exhaling mentally repeat and
visualize the number three three times.
To help you learn to relax physically at level three
I'm going to direct your attention to different parts of your
body.
Relax your Relax your scalp.
Relax your forehead.
Relax your eyes and the tissue surrounding your eyes.
With a slight smile. Relax your face, relax your throat and neck
area externally and internally.
Relax your shoulders, arms and hands.
Take a deep breath, and as you exhale, relax your chest
externally and internally.
Take a deep breath and as you exhale relax your abdominal area
Relax your thighs.
Relax your knees.
Relax your calves.
Relax your feet.
You are now at a deeper, healthier level of mind, deeper than
before.
This is your physical relaxation level 3. Three, whenever you
mentally repeat and visualize the number three, your body will
relax as completely as you are now and more so every time
you practice.
To enter mental relaxation level two, take a deep breath and
while exhaling, mentally you repeat and visualize number two
three times and you are at level two a deeper level in
three level two is for mental relaxation where noises will not
distract you instead noises will help you to relax mentally more
and more to to improve mental relaxation at level two.
Practice visualizing tranquil and passive scenes
in a holographic, three -dimensional manner,
engaging all of your subjective senses.
Do that now.
Take another deep breath.
And while exhaling, mentally repeat and visualize Visualize
number one three times.
You are now at level one, the basic plane level, a deeper,
healthier level of mind.
To help you enter a deeper, healthier level of mind, I am
going to count from ten to one.
On each descending number, you will feel yourself going deeper
and you will enter a deeper, healthier level of mind. 9, 10,
9, feel going deeper, 8, 7, 6, deeper and deeper, 5, 4,
3, deeper and deeper
to
one.
You are now at a deeper,
healthier level of mind,
deeper than before.
It is a wonderful feeling to be deeply relaxed,
a very healthy state of being.
Effective sensory projection statements for success.
I will be speaking in your place I am now able to
function my intelligence by developing my sensing faculties and
to experience myself as any point place level or depth so as
to be aware of any actions taking place I am able to
function in non -locality regarding time and space i am aware
that intelligence exists at all levels and depths in the
universe and therefore i can attune to all information i am now
able to use my sensing faculties and to experience myself as any
matter kingdom mineral plant animal and human if this is what I
desire to do I am now able to detect abnormalities whenever such
abnormalities exist within any kingdom any level, any depth.
I am now able to apply corrective measures and to bring back
to normalcy any abnormality found within any kingdom, any level,
and any depth.
Quantum energy is available at any level to be acted upon to
create through the subjective and objective dimensions.
We will now impress new information for your benefit,
the mental screen.
To locate your mental screen,
begin with your eyes closed.
Turn slightly upward from the horizontal plane of sight at an
angle of approximately 20 degrees.
The area that you perceive with your mind is your mental screen.
Without using your eyelids as screens, sense your mental screen
to be out, away from your body.
To improve the use of your mental screen, project images or
mental pictures onto the screen,
especially images having color.
Concentrate on mentally sensing and visualizing true color.
Programming the HoloViewing technique that you can use for
problem solving.
Whenever you need to solve a problem, make a decision, or obtain
guidance with the HoloViewing technique,
Proceed in the following manner.
Project the image of the problem or present situation onto your
mental screen as a two -dimensional
dull gray tone image similar to a black and white Polaroid
photograph in order to make a brief study of the problem.
make the problem image smaller smaller and smaller until it
completely disappears at that moment when the problem image
disappears create an image of the solution and allow it to
approach you by making it bigger and bigger be sure to project
a bright clear and colorful dynamic solution image.
Stop the approaching image and modify, improve or change any
element of the image that needs improvement.
When the image of the solution is exactly as you desire it
to be, continue allowing it to approach you by getting bigger
still until it wraps around you and you find yourself within the
image in a holographic three -dimensional experience with a 360
degree spherical view at this point you may experience yourself
fully and completely engaging all of your mental senses together
with coherent emotions.
You may also experience yourself in a second -person point of
view. In other words, you may experience a solution image from
the other person or person's point of view.
In addition, you may also project yourself outside the scene and
experience observing the solution image from a third -person
perspective, the observer.
This allows you to have a full holographic experience that you
can then move forward into the future through hollow movement,
experiencing the solution in a past -ten sense from the
perspective of whole and complete.
Mentally, talk to source energy within you and through the
hollow viewing technique, share your desires charged with
coherent emotions with your source energy.
Express great gratitude, appreciation,
compassion or love to source energy deep within you.
Take for granted that your source energy will assist you with
manifesting your solution.
During the next three days look for indications that point to
the solution.
Every time you think of the project think of the solution that
you have created with the hollow viewing technique and do so in
a past tense sense.
It is time to work on one problem case using the hollow
viewing technique. Project the image of the problem or present
situation onto your mental screen as a two -dimensional dull
gray tone image similar to a black and white Polaroid photograph
in order to make a brief study of the problem.
make the problem image smaller smaller and smaller until it
completely disappears.
At that moment when the problem image disappears, create an
image of the solution and allow it to approach you by making
it bigger and bigger.
Be sure to project a bright, clear, colorful and dynamic
solution image.
stop the approaching image and modify improve or change any
element of the image that needs improvement created exactly how
you wish it to be
when the image of the solution is exactly as you desire it
to be continue allowing it to approach you by getting bigger and
bigger still until it wraps around you and you find yourself
within the image in a holographic three -dimensional experience
with a 360 degree spherical view take a deep breath and relax
at this point experience yourself fully and completely engaging
all of your mental senses together with coherent emotion bring
about desire Desire, belief and expectation, faith.
You may also experience yourself in a second person point of
view.
In other words, you may experience the solution image from the
other person or person's point of view.
In addition, you may also project yourself outside the scene and
experience observing the solution image from a third -person
perspective, the observer.
Engage in the experience fully and completely in a holographic
manner that you can then move forward into the future through
holomovement,
experiencing the solution in a past tense sense.
From the perspective of whole and complete.
Mentally, talk to source energy within you and through the
hollow viewing technique, share your desires charged with
coherent emotions emotions of gratitude appreciation compassion
and love with a great desire to manifest this outcome a belief
in yourself and your worth in your ability to make it happen
in source energy helping you along the way and an expectation
that it will will happen.
Take for granted that your Source Energy will assist you with
manifesting your solution
as you sleep and come close to the Delta Doorway during your
dream sleep cycles.
during the next three days look for indications that point to
the solution
and every time you think of the project think of the solution
that you created with a hollow viewing technique and do so in
a past tense sense Expect this or better than this to manifest.
Now take a deep breath.
Exhale and go deeper and deeper, allowing yourself to enter
deep, natural, healthy sleep, expecting to awaken happier,
healthier, with a knowing that great things are to come.
Breathe slowly, deeply, rhythmically and enter deep, natural,
healthy sleep.
Allow the sound of the background to deepen you. Relax. Relax.
Thank you.